TIANA HO'OLANA HUSTED

Eugene, OR | (971)404-1043 | tiana.husted@gmail.com | LinkedIn | GitHub

SUMMARY

Software engineer and web developer with a background in tech-based art and a passion for learning new technologies. Extensive experience with custom interface design for interactive art installations, utilizing microprocessors and sensors. Interested in creating and improving digital experiences through the continued study of human/interface interaction. Natural problem solver with a commitment to approaching any project with innovation, thoroughness, and creativity.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: JavaScript, JQuery, HTML, CSS

Applications: Bootstrap, NodeJS, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, Handlebars.js, ReactJS

Visual Programming Environments: Max/MSP

Creative Programming Environments: Arduino IDE, Processing

EXPERIENCE

Stereo Technician/Operations Manager Vintage Stereos LLC

January 2022-Present

- Repair and restore vintage, solid-state audio equipment in a safe and timely manner
- Meticulously solder replacement components to modernize intricate electrical circuits
- Utilize diagnostic tools to accurately troubleshoot and resolve issues
- Carry out procedures to calibrate and extensively test equipment before returning it to clients
- Make additions to standing inventory lists so necessary parts orders can be placed
- Interface with clients daily to maintain a positive customer experience
- Delegate tasks to customer service and shipping employees

Installation Artist House of Strange Rituals

June 2018-Present

- Develop, construct, and maintain interactive, sound, and lighting systems in art exhibitions of varying sizes
- Engineer circuits, design custom software, program microprocessors, work with numerous sensors, design power distribution systems, and produce original sound for art pieces
- Work with various sound and video technologies, including projectors and projection mapping software
- 2019 Recipient of competitive Black Rock City Honoraria Grant

Audio Technician Velvet Thunder Sound Systems

July 2018-March 2020

- Operated specialized sound equipment for theater events
- Planned and executed equipment set-up in collaboration with touring performers and crews
- Implemented excellent problem-solving abilities in a fast-paced technical environment
- Demonstrated adaptability during unpredictable events and strong attention to detail
- Constructed and deconstructed stages and sound systems for festival events

EDUCATION

Certificate in Full Stack Web Development University of Oregon, *Portland, OR*April 2020-October 2020

• A 24-week intensive program focused on gaining technical programming skills in HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap, Node Js, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, Handelbars.js & ReactJS

Bachelor of Science: Music Technology University of Oregon

September 2016-December 2018

Eugene, OR

• A 4-year Bachelor's degree focused on electronic composition with audio and visual elements, sound design, and musical interface design

Associate's Degree: General Studies/Music Lane Community College

September 2013-June 2016

Eugene, OR

• A 2-year Associate's degree with an extended focus on music theory and composition, music technology, and audio engineering